[BILLY] Do you know what caused the fire?
[CLERK] No one knows, miss.
All I heard was that Mariela survived.
And so did her youngest daughter.
But her eldest daughter died.
[JORDAN] When did the fire happen?
[CLERK] About 12 to 13 years ago, I think.
[BILLY] But the father
wasn't with them?
[CLERK] No,
he wasn't.
The rumor is that
Mariela's husband left her.
You sure about this, Billy?
You don't want Oliver to go home for now?
He's growing up, Auntie Pres.
You okay with this?
For now.
Look how happy he was with his dad.
Dear.
- Ma.
- Where's your laundry?
[BEA] No need. I'll do it myself.
[MARIELA] Let me do it. Just go to work.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
How do you do that?
Compartmentalizing.
It's like you don't even think about…
About what?
About Oliver.
Hmm.
I just didn't expect that
you'd let him.
I just gave Oliver what--
What he wanted?
What he needed.
I kept it a secret from him for years.
Because I wanted to protect him.
But you know, dude,
when I saw him with that man,
I knew I was wrong to decide for Oliver.
Because all he wants is to know his dad.
Mr. Dino.
Good morning.
Why'd you choose to join our group?
From what I can see,
you're the nicest people here.
What do you know?
Nothing.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
What do you know?
[STAMMERS] N-Nothing.
Is there something I should know?
What makes LoveList different
from all the other swipe apps?
Good question.
Well, LoveList isn't based on swipes.
Our matching engine is driven by
how the users behave online.
We focus on behavior, not just profiles.
That's where the real signal is.
After reviewing your proposal
and hearing you talk now,
I'm in.
- Great. Great! Thank you.
- All right, thank you.
- Thank you for the trust, Mr. Fabrizio.
- Oh, please, just call me Peter.
- [BILLY] Thank you, Peter.
- [PETER] All right.
- [JORDAN] Thank you, Peter.
- [PETER] Of course.
Enrico, let's meet. We need to talk.
Ah, okay, okay.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
"Marj Quinto: Love has no
borders, neither do we!
#LovelistGoesGlobal"
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
The food here's pretty good, Billy.
Hm, here, Billy. Have some.
I'm good. Keep eating.
Here, do you want to order more?
[BILLY] Let's order some more.
Um…
dessert?
Oh! Can I get the apple crumble?
Please. Once in a while is okay, right?
- Hmm…
- [OLIVER] Please?
But they don't have a sugar-free option.
Let's drop by the shop we frequent at
on the way home instead.
Okay?
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy.
Again, I'm sorry.
Are you okay now?
[BILLY] Are you happy?
Yes.
But… are you no longer mad?
You know that I love you very much, right?
So that means
you're gonna let me see Papa again?
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mm.
Thank you, Billy!
- Thank you!
- Mmm!
Thank you, thank you!
[OLIVER] I promise you.
I'll do my best in my studies.
I'll get my grades up even higher.
Once I graduate,
I'll take care of you and Auntie.
Mmm.
- [OLIVER] Tight hug! Tighter!
- [BILLY GROANING]
Can I still order?
Hmm.
- Bro Dude?
- Mm-hmm.
Bro Dude!
Hm?
Bro Dude, Billy and I are okay now.
She let me see Papa again.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Qualified.
As long as you two made up.
Yes. Let's eat!
- [JORDAN] Let's!
- [OLIVER] Okay.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING]
Are you gonna order?
[JORDAN SIGHS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
I hope you can forgive me, Precious.
I never meant to hurt you.
I didn't come here
to listen to your explanation.
- But, Pres--
- Listen.
Billy agreed. You can meet with Oliver
after his classes are over.
4:30 to 5:30.
You can meet up at your house.
But Billy said I have
to be there too.
Is that good with you?
Pres…
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hi-yah! Hi-yah!
- [SIX-BUTTONS CLACKING]
[JORDAN] Are you sure about your decision?
My brother's all grown up.
And really smart too.
I just want to give him the chance
to meet his father,
even just for a little while.
Then it's up to him
after he gets to know him.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello?!
Hello?
Sorry. I was just surprised.
You're just so mature in what you said.
But really, I wish…
I wish I had your courage.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OLIVER] Ugh, I lost.
Jordan, Billy, come on.
Let's play over there. Please.
- Oh, of course!
- Enough with your talking.
- Let's go!
- Let's play.
- Come on.
- It's playtime.
Last one there is a buzzkill.
I'm really sorry.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMAN] What the hell?!
The road is so wide!
You're blocking the way!
- I'm just over here on the side!
- Ugh! Don't you have eyes?!
Stop! Just get out of here!
- Dang it!
- Idiot!
- Come on.
Let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Mariela?
I saw my husband.
The one who hasn't contacted me in years.
I caught him
with another woman again.
He has a new mistress.
[SIGHS] Mariela…
She took him away from me!
I wanted to kill them!
If it wouldn't have meant
leaving my daughter behind,
if it wouldn't have landed me in prison,
I would've killed them!
My husband and his lover!
Mariela, what you're thinking is wrong.
You can't do that.
What about having an affair
with a married man?
Is that right?
Huh? Answer me.
What? Mariel, please.
I don't understand what you're saying.
You'll understand.
I'll make you understand
how painful it is.
I'll make all of you feel it!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What's going on here?
Ma'am, are you okay?
Ma'am, please leave.
Please.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
Wait, wait!
- Step back.
- Hey!
- Hey! Don't let him win!
- Wait.
- I'll do it.
- You take over for now, Billy.
- Your turn.
- Let me win, okay!
- I can do this.
- Go, go!
- [SCREAMS]
- Oh!
- [OLIVER] Oh no!
- There!
- Wait! Oh my God!
- Oh!
- We're almost there!
- We'll catch up.
- No, dude.
- Go, Billy!
- Go!
- Wait!
- Go, go!
- Hurry!
- Cheater! Cheater!
[CHEERING]
- Yeah! Let's go!
- Let's go!
- Billy! Billy!
- I give up.
Okay! Whew, it's hot.
Ugh, okay.
[LAUGHING]
- Next game!
- Let's go.
- Next game, come on.
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
- No!
- [CHEERING]
[BILLY] That's enough.
- [BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [EXCITED, INDISTINCT SHOUTS]
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[BILLY] Go, Oliver.
[BILLY] Wow!
[PINS CLATTER]
[CHEERING]
- [OLIVER CHEERING]
- [BILLY] Okay!
[INDISTINCT SHOUT]
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
- Yes! We won!
- [CHEERING]
[SCREAMS]
- Amazing!
- [OLIVER GRUNTS]
You're so good.
- [JORDAN] Nice one.
- [OLIVER] Strike.
♪ I'll hold your hand in the madness ♪
♪ Run to me if they cast you aside ♪
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Oh, he's done for.
- [JORDAN SINGS]
The boss is really in love.
He's completely smitten.
Yeah, he really is.
[SLAPS HANDS TOGETHER]
"To my beautiful Valerie…"
- Hey! Hey!
- Wow!
That's for Valerie?
Obviously. That's what it says, right?
Guys, whose is this?
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
- It's Lover Boy's!
Looks like he's going to
try his luck with Valerie.
- [RAIN GUSHING]
- [ROBBIE] No!
Oh, what's wrong with that?
Bro, if you have feelings for her,
just tell her.
What's important
is that you're being honest.
That's true.
- That's right.
- Oh, is that true, boss?
- You go first.
- Hey!
What?
Oh, no, no. Uh…
You write something here first, boss.
- It should come from your heart.
- Boss, come on.
You write songs, don't you?
Maybe you can share your talent
when it comes to words.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
There.
"To my beautiful Valerie…"
Yeah, that's all I've written so far.
- Add more.
- [CHUCKLES]
[ROBBIE] That's all I can think of.
[OLIVER] Billy is my hero.
When our parents died,
Billy worked hard to take care of me,
send me to school,
and give me a good life.
She taught me that I should
work hard and be brave.
Because Billy never backs down.
Especially when it comes to family.
So for Billy, I'll work hard too.
So that one day,
I'll be the one to take care of her.
And I'll be her hero.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Looks like my enemies backed off, Billy.
Yeah. I wonder why.
Maybe they're scared of you.
- Maybe they're scared of you.
- Me?!
Do I look scary?
Very good!
Congratulations!
You win one million pesos!
Very good!
Just one million?
It should be five million!
- I studied hard, you know.
- It can't be five million!
It should actually be 10 million
because I memorized that.
- You're our baby.
- Baby.
- No! No!
- You're still a baby.
- Baby.
- Smells like a baby.
- No, no, no!
- You're our baby.
- Right?
- No!
- You're still a baby.
- I'm not a baby!
- Drink your water, baby.
- No!
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Lydia, thank you for coming with me.
I didn't want to bother Billy anymore.
Are you really sure about this?
I just want to understand
what Mariela and her daughter
are going through.
Well, why don't they try to understand
what you and Billy
are going through instead?
Lydia, we're from the Angels of Grace.
We need to be more understanding.
I think this might also be a good chance
to find out why
they are so angry with Billy.
So you think this can still be resolved
with talking and counseling?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mariela?
Bea?
Let's just leave.
Wait a minute.
Mariela?
Bea?
Sis, let's just leave.
It's okay.
Mariela?
Bea?
Oh, what happened here?
[LYDIA] Sis, let's just leave. Come on!
[PRECIOUS] Wait a second.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PRECIOUS] Mariela?
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE SHUTTERING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[MUSIC TURNS SUSPENSEFUL]
- [PRECIOUS] Wait a second.
- [LYDIA] Someone's inside.
[LYDIA] Let's get going.
Let's get out of here.
[MARIELA] What are you doing here?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mariela.
Mariela, what happened to you?
I was cooking.
[MARIELA] I got hurt.
But I asked you,
what are you doing here?
Mariela, I just came here to clarify
what you said earlier.
Were you referring to me and Billy?
So what if I was?
You're threatening to kill us?
People who deceive and steal
deserve to die.
Did we deceive you?
[PRECIOUS] Did we steal from you?
And what's the deal with
Billy's pictures upstairs?
When has Billy ever wronged you?
Billy's not the only one who wronged us.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You've wronged us too.
Mariela, what are you even talking about?
I will fight for our rights!
What rights are you
even talking about, Mariela?
[MARIELA] I won't let me or
my daughter get wronged again!
- Damn you!
- Stop that!
- Mariela, stop that!
- Mariela!
- This is for my daughter!
- [LYDIA] Enough!
- Mariela!
- You bastards!
- Damn you!
- [men] That's enough! Stop!
[MARIELA] Just you wait!
I will come back for you!
I will kill you!
You bastards!
Damn you all!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you all right?
You saw how happy
he was earlier, didn't you?
Didn't I tell you
that decision was for Oliver?
But is it the right choice?
Well, we'll never know unless we try.
[DOOR OPENING]
Okay then. Bye-bye.
[BILLY] Auntie Pres.
Are you all right?
Did you get to talk with Ms. Mariela?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
Auntie Pres, even if you were trespassing,
what she did was still wrong!
We should report her!
You got hurt.
[PRECIOUS] We were shocked
when we saw that there.
[WOMAN] Your mother
almost murdered someone!
Now I understand why you're
so furious at that Billy!
[BEA] I will avenge us.
I will avenge us both, okay?
Auntie, can we invite Papa
to my moving-up ceremony?
I got high honors.
[ENRICO] Remember this, son.
From now on, I'll always be here for you.
You're right, Precious.
I deceived you.
But the love I have for my children
and for you
is real.
Dude? Bea and her mother
are now gone.
Isn't this better?
For them to just go away?
If it were just about me,
fine, I'd let it slide.
But we're talking about Auntie Pres.
I won't just let it go. Sorry.
I'm just worried about you.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]